Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
- Box: 93, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: College Facts Chart, Publication (Box 93, Folder 1)
    Author: The National Beta Club
  - Item 2: Total Enrollment, Publication (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Residence and Migration, Publication (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Box: 93, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: College Purpose and Community Need, Publication (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Box: 93, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: University Extension Reconsidered, Publication (Box 93, Folder 3)
    Author: University of Leicester
- Box: 93, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Industrial Map of Utica, Publication (Box 93, Folder 4)
    Author: Utica Chamber of Commerce
- Box: 93, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Cacotopias and Utopias, Publication (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Box: 93, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Holidays with Pay Act, 1938; Publication (Box 93, Folder 6)
    Author: Great Britain Parliament
  - Item 2: Catering Wages Commission, 1947; Publication (Box 93, Folder 6)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Labour and National Service
  - Item 3: Vacations, 1946; Publication (Box 93, Folder 6)
    Notes: September 1946
- Box: 93, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Annual Vacations and Vacation Laws, 1967; Publication (Box 93, Folder 7)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Education and Labor
  - Item 2: Holiday and Leave Practices, Publication (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Vacation Policies, Notices, Memos, Forms, Publication (Box 93, Folder 7)
    Author: Dartnell Corporation
- Box: 93, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Vacations for Office Workers, Publication (Box 93, Folder 8)
    Author: Metropolitan Life Insurance Company
  - Item 2: Recent Trends in Vacation Policies for Wage Earners, 1935; Publication (Box 93, Folder 8)
    Author: Eleanor Davis
- Box: 93, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Ferieloven, 1967; Publication (Box 93, Folder 9)
    Author: Paul Kufahl
    Language: Danish.
- Box: 93, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Laki Tyontekijain Vuosilomasta, Publication (Box 93, Folder 10)
    Author: Valtion Painatuskeskus
    Language: Finnish.
- Box: 93, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Bundesurlaubsgesetz, Publication (Box 93, Folder 11)
    Author: C.H. Beck Munchen und Berlin
    Language: German.
  - Item 2: Das Urlaubsrecht, 1968; Publication (Box 93, Folder 11)
    Author: Richard Boorberg Verlag
    Notes: November 1968
  - Item 3: Annual Holidays, Publication (Box 93, Folder 11)
    Author: Federal Ministry of Labour and the Social Structure
- Box: 93, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Implications for Management of Longer Standard Holidays, Publication (Box 93, Folder 12)
    Author: Hugh Clegg, P.S. Narasimhan
- Box: 93, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Normas de Derecho Vacacional en Guatemala, 1965; Publication (Box 93, Folder 13)
    Author: Emilio Zebadua Garcia
    Language: Spanish.
- Box: 93, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Innstilling om Ferie og Fritid for Jordbruksbefolkningen, 1968; Publication (Box 93, Folder 14)
    Author: Engers Boktrykkeri
    Language: Norwegian.
- Box: 93, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Kompendium I Semesterratt, Publication (Box 93, Folder 15)
    Author: Lennart Geijer
    Language: Swedish.
- Box: 93, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Employment Opportunities for Vietnam Era Veterans, 1968; Publication (Box 93, Folder 16)
    Notes: April 2, 1968
  - Item 2: Reemployment Rights, Publication (Box 93, Folder 16)
- Box: 93, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Employment Services for Veterans, Publication (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Military Service and War Job Clauses, 1942; Publication (Box 93, Folder 17)
    Notes: August 1942
  - Item 3: You and the Returning Veteran, Publication (Box 93, Folder 17)
    Author: Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Co
- Box: 93, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Employment of Ex-Servicemen in the Iron and Steel Industry, 1946; Publication (Box 93, Folder 18)
    Author: American Iron and Steel Institute
    Notes: October 1946
  - Item 2: Re-Employment of Ex-Servicemen in the Iron and Steel Industry, 1944; Publication (Box 93, Folder 18)
    Notes: August 1944
- Box: 93, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Veterans Pension Act, 1966; Publication (Box 93, Folder 19)
    Notes: October 18, 1966
  - Item 2: Veterans in Public Service Act, 1968; Publication (Box 93, Folder 19)
    Notes: March 12, 1968
  - Item 3: Employment for Returning Veterans, 1968; Publication (Box 93, Folder 19)
    Notes: February 28, 1968
  - Item 4: Work Experience of War Veterans, 1965; Publication (Box 93, Folder 19)
    Notes: November 4, 1965
  - Item 5: Reemployment Rights Handbook, 1958; Publication (Box 93, Folder 19)
    Notes: May 1958
  - Item 6: A Survey of Socially and Economically Disadvantaged Vietnam Era Veterans, 1969; Publication (Box 93, Folder 19)
- Box: 93, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Survey of Veteran Preference Policies, Publication (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Veteran Preference in Federal Employment, Publication (Box 93, Folder 20)
- Box: 93, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Veterans' Job Reinstatement Rights, 1954; Publication (Box 93, Folder 21)
    Author: Army Times Publishing
  - Item 2: Serving Those Who Served, 1965; Publication (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Vocational Rehabilitation for Service Disabled, 1965; Publication (Box 93, Folder 21)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Veterans' Affairs
    Notes: June 1, 1965
  - Item 4: Serving Those Who Served, 1965; Publication (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Assistance to Veterans of Vietnam or Elsewhere in Obtaining Suitable Employment, 1968; Publication (Box 93, Folder 21)
    Notes: February 20, 1968
- Box: 93, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Federal Benefits for Veterans & Dependents, 1969; Publication (Box 93, Folder 22)
    Notes: January 1969
  - Item 2: Group Life Insurance for the Uniformed Services, 1965; Publication (Box 93, Folder 22)
    Notes: September 15, 1965
- Box: 93, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Serving Those Who Served, 1967; Publication (Box 93, Folder 23)
- Box: 93, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Improving Educational and Training Programs for Veterans, 1968; Publication (Box 93, Folder 24)
    Notes: July 11, 1968
  - Item 2: Bills Related to Education and Training Programs, 1968; Publication (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Digest and Analysis of the Cold War GI Bill, 1966; Publication (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Education and Training in Veterans' Administration, 1966; Publication (Box 93, Folder 24)
- Box: 93, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 93, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Retirement Systems for Judges, Commissioners and Clerks, 1967; Publication (Box 93, Folder 25)
    Author: Virginia Department of Purchases and Supply
- Box: 93, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Inter-American Cooperation in Vocational Education, 1950; Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    Author: Fernando Romero
  - Item 2: The Organization and Administration of Vocational-Technical Courses in Secondary Schools, 1950; Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    Notes: January 1, 1950
  - Item 3: A Study of Industrial Teacher Education at the Graduate Level, 1941; Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    Author: American Vocational Association
    Notes: December 1941
  - Item 4: Organization and Administration of General Occupational Courses, 1940; Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Industrial Education for Girls and Women, 1944; Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: Education in a Technological Society, 1952; Publication (Box 93, Folder 26)
    Author: Unesco
- Box: 93, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Organization for Rehabilitation Through Training, 1967; Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    Author: American ORT Education
  - Item 2: Vocational Education Amendments, 1968; Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Public Education and Manpower Development, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
    Author: Ford Foundation
  - Item 4: Vocational Hand Arts and Crafts Program for Adults, Publication (Box 93, Folder 27)
- Box: 93, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 93, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Feasibility Study of Extension Training and Education, 1967; Publication (Box 93, Folder 28)
    Author: Vermont Office of Technical Services
    Notes: September 1967
  - Item 2: Adapting Educational Change to Manpower Needs, Publication (Box 93, Folder 28)
- Box: 93, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 93, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Disciplina del Collocamento Addestramento Professionale, 1968; Publication (Box 93, Folder 29)
    Author: L. Di G. Pirola
    Language: Italian.
  - Item 2: Vocational Education in Colorado, 1966; Publication (Box 93, Folder 29)
    Author: Colorado Legislative Council
  - Item 3: Effects of Vocational Training and Other Factors on Employment Experience, 1966; Publication (Box 93, Folder 29)
    Author: North Star Research and Development Institute
    Notes: April 30, 1966
  - Item 4: Guide to the Manpower Development and Training Act, 1964; Publication (Box 93, Folder 29)
    Author: Idaho State Board for Vocational Education
    Notes: April 1964
  - Item 5: A Survey of the SEATO Skilled Labour Project, Publication (Box 93, Folder 29)
    Author: Southeast Asia Treaty Organization
  - Item 6: Instituto Nacional de Formacion de Instructores, 1967; Publication (Box 93, Folder 29)
    Author: Ministerio de Trabajo y Comunidades
  - Item 7: Follow-Up of 1965 Graduates, Publication (Box 93, Folder 29)
    Author: J. Kenneth Little, Richard W. Whinfield
  - Item 8: Vocational Improvement Centres, Publication (Box 93, Folder 29)
    Author: Gaston V. Rimlinger & Carolyn Stremlau
  - Item 9: Adapting Educational Change to Manpower Needs, Publication (Box 93, Folder 29)
  - Item 10: Adult Vocational Training, Publication (Box 93, Folder 29)
    Author: Ministries of Labour and Social Affairs
- Box: 93, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 93, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Vocational Education, Publication (Box 93, Folder 30)
    Author: Alice Songe
- Box: 93, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 93, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Some References on Vocational Education, Publication (Box 93, Folder 31)
- Box: 93, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 93, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Manpower Development and Training, 1963; Publication (Box 93, Folder 32)
    Author: Mary R. Heslet
    Notes: December 3, 1963
  - Item 2: Vocational and Technical Education, 1966; Publication (Box 93, Folder 32)
    Author: Princeton University
    Notes: September 1966
  - Item 3: Resources for Office Education Programs, Publication (Box 93, Folder 32)
- Box: 93, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 93, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Conference on Employment and Education, 1963; Publication (Box 93, Folder 33)
    Author: Saskatchewan Association for Adult Education
    Notes: April 9-11, 1963
  - Item 2: Federal Expenditures for Vocational Training, Publication (Box 93, Folder 33)
    Author: Canada Department of Citizenship and Immigration
  - Item 3: Federal Expenditures for Vocational Training, Publication (Box 93, Folder 33)
- Box: 93, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 93, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Automobile and Diesel Mechanics Course, Publication (Box 93, Folder 34)
    Author: Hanson Mechanical Trade School
  - Item 2: Hanson Mechanical Trade School, Publication (Box 93, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: Textile Scholarships, Publication (Box 93, Folder 34)
    Author: New England Textile Foundation
  - Item 4: Program of Studies, Publication (Box 93, Folder 34)
    Author: Beverly Trade School
- Box: 93, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Televison and Radio Servicing, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
    Author: YMCA Trade and Technical School
  - Item 2: Television and Radio Servicing, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Consider Mechanical Drafting, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
    Author: Connecticut State Department of Education
  - Item 4: Hanson Mechanical Trade School, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Item 5: Automotive Mechanic, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Item 6: Practical Designing and Dressmaking, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Item 7: Printing, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Item 8: The Plumbing Trade, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Item 9: Electrical Work, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Item 10: Carpentry, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Item 11: Beauty Culture, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Item 12: Machine Trade, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Item 13: Food Trades, Publication (Box 93, Folder 35)
- Box: 93, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 93, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Guideposts in the Vocational High Schools, Publication (Box 93, Folder 36)
    Author: New York City Board of Education
- Box: 93, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 93, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Clerical and Record Keeping Occupations, Publication (Box 93, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: Stenographic - Secretarial Occupations, Publication (Box 93, Folder 37)
- Box: 93, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 93, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Decision, 1963; Publication (Box 93, Folder 38)
    Author: European Economic Community Council of Ministers
    Language: French; German; Spanish; Dutch.
- Box: 93, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 93, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Vocational, Technical, and Adult Education, 1965; Publication (Box 93, Folder 39)
    Author: Florida Department of Education
- Box: 93, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 93, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Technological and Management Education, Publication (Box 93, Folder 40)
    Author: Denning Pearson
  - Item 2: Industrial Training Act, 1964; Publication (Box 93, Folder 40)
  - Item 3: Better Opportunities in Technical Education, 1961; Publication (Box 93, Folder 40)
    Notes: January 1961
  - Item 4: Technical Education in Britain, Publication (Box 93, Folder 40)
    Author: Great Britain Central Office of Information
- Box: 93, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 93, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Vocational Education in Israel, 1967; Publication (Box 93, Folder 41)
    Author: Perez F. Harburger
  - Item 2: Israel's Programme for Training Opportunities, Publication (Box 93, Folder 41)
    Author: Israel's Programme for Training Opportunities
- Box: 94, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Industrial Arts for Kentucky High Schools, 1948; Publication (Box 94, Folder 1)
    Author: Kentucky Department of Education
    Notes: July 1948
  - Item 2: State Plan of Operation for Area Vocational Schools in Kentucky, Publication (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Box: 94, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: 25 Years of Progress, Publication (Box 94, Folder 2)
    Author: Baltimore Department of Education
- Box: 94, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Need for Vocational Education, 1948; Publication (Box 94, Folder 3)
    Author: New Jersey Department of Education
- Box: 94, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Free Choice Vocational Trade Training, Publication (Box 94, Folder 4)
    Author: The Lavanburg-Corner House
- Box: 94, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Scope and Sequence of Vocational High School Courses of Study, 1943; Publication (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Box: 94, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Education for Occupations, Publication (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Vocational Education in the Public Schools of New York State, Publication (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Box: 94, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Costs and Returns of Technical Education, Publication (Box 94, Folder 7)
    Author: Adger B. Carroll & Loren A. Ihnen
- Box: 94, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Problems in the Further Development of Vocational Education in South Carolina in the Years Ahead, Publication (Box 94, Folder 8)
    Author: Clemson University
- Box: 94, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Trade and Industrial Education, Publication (Box 94, Folder 9)
    Author: Ouachita Valley Vocational School
  - Item 2: Trade and Industrial Education, Publication (Box 94, Folder 9)
    Author: Illinois State Board for Vocational Education
  - Item 3: Administrative and Supervisory Provisions, 1947; Publication (Box 94, Folder 9)
    Author: Ohio State Board for Vocational Education
    Notes: June 15, 1947
- Box: 94, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Sistema Podqotovki I Povyshewiia Kvalifikatsii Kadrov, 1954; Publication (Box 94, Folder 10)
    Author: A. Karpenko
  - Item 2: The Future Development of Higher Technological Education, 1950; Publication (Box 94, Folder 10)
    Author: Great Britain Ministry of Education
  - Item 3: Vocational Training, Publication (Box 94, Folder 10)
- Box: 94, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Vocational Industrial Education in Newly Developing Nations, Publication (Box 94, Folder 11)
    Author: Stanford University
- Box: 94, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Vocational Education and Training in the Soviet Union, Publication (Box 94, Folder 12)
    Author: British Association for Commercial and Industrial Education
- Box: 94, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Technical Education in Scotland, 1961; Publication (Box 94, Folder 13)
    Author: Scottish Education Department
- Box: 94, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Vocational Training, 1964; Publication (Box 94, Folder 14)
    Author: Valentin F. Cuevas
  - Item 2: Intensive Vocational Training, 1964; Publication (Box 94, Folder 14)
    Author: Publicaciones Espanolas
- Box: 94, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Vocational and Non-Academic Study in Sweden, Publication (Box 94, Folder 15)
    Author: Sweden-America Foundation
- Box: 94, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Community Surveys in Determining Needs for Vocational Industrial Education, 1945; Publication (Box 94, Folder 16)
    Notes: January 2, 1945
- Box: 94, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Federal Programs in Job Training and Retraining, 1967; Publication (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Focus on Vocational Education, 1967; Publication (Box 94, Folder 17)
    Notes: December 8, 1967
  - Item 3: Vocational Education and Manpower Needs, Publication (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Vocational Programs, 1969; Publication (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Vocational Education, 1968; Publication (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Industry and Community Leaders in Education, Publication (Box 94, Folder 17)
    Author: Samuel M. Burt
- Box: 94, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Vocational and Industrial Arts Education, Publication (Box 94, Folder 18)
- Box: 94, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Industrial Arts, Publication (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: The Vocational Education Act, Publication (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Public Vocational Education Programs, Publication (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Occupational Education, Publication (Box 94, Folder 19)
    Author: American Association of Junior Colleges
  - Item 5: Vocational Education, Publication (Box 94, Folder 19)
    Author: National Center for Educational Statistics
  - Item 6: Job-Oriented Education Programs for the Disadvantaged, Publication (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: Vocational Education and Federal Policy, Publication (Box 94, Folder 19)
    Author: Sar A. Levitan
  - Item 8: Target: Employment!, Publication (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: The Role of the Secondary Schools in the Preparation of Youth for Employment, 1967; Publication (Box 94, Folder 19)
    Author: Pennsylvania State University
    Notes: February 1967
- Box: 94, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Vocational-Technical Program Development, 1965; Publication (Box 94, Folder 20)
    Notes: October 1965
  - Item 2: Federal Programs in Job Training and Retraining, 1967; Publication (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Basic Planning Guide for Vocational and Technical Education Facilities, Publication (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: The Process and Product of Trade and Industrial High School Level Vocational Education in the United States, 1966; Publication (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: Private Vocational Schools, Publication (Box 94, Folder 20)
    Author: A. Harvey Belitsky
- Box: 94, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Trade and Industrial Education for Girls and Women, Publication (Box 94, Folder 21)
- Box: 94, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Looking Ahead to the World of Work, Publication (Box 94, Folder 22)
    Author: Canada Department of Labour
  - Item 2: A Job Guide, Publication (Box 94, Folder 22)
    Author: Alabama Department of Industrial Relations
  - Item 3: The World of Work Conference, 1962; Publication (Box 94, Folder 22)
    Notes: July 27-28, 1962
  - Item 4: Detroit Metropolitan Area Survey of Training Needs, Publication (Box 94, Folder 22)
    Author: Michigan Employment Security Commission
  - Item 5: Problems in Accomplishing Objectives of the Work Incentive Program, 1971; Publication (Box 94, Folder 22)
    Notes: September 24, 1971
  - Item 6: Counseling and Employment Service for Youth, 1962; Publication (Box 94, Folder 22)
    Notes: November 1962
- Box: 94, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Effects of National Service on the Education and Employment of Young Men, 1955; Publication (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Job Guide for Young Workers, Publication (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: Your Job and Your Future, Publication (Box 94, Folder 23)
    Author: New York University
  - Item 4: Let's Learn From Youth, Publication (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: Helping the Job Seeker to Help Himself, 1949; Publication (Box 94, Folder 23)
    Author: New York State Department of Labor
    Notes: November 7, 1949
  - Item 6: Youth and Jobs, Publication (Box 94, Folder 23)
    Author: Charles E. Merrill Books
- Box: 94, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Career Opportunity Guide, 1966; Publication (Box 94, Folder 24)
    Author: Michigan State University
  - Item 2: An Approach to Individual Analysis in Educational and Vocational Guidance, Publication (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Your Future Job -- Choice or Chance, Publication (Box 94, Folder 24)
    Author: Oregon Bureau of Labor
  - Item 4: A Leader's Guide for Group Guidance in Creative Job Search Techniques, Publication (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: The Oregon Pilot Project in Teaching Creative Job Search Techniques, Publication (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Guidelines for Organizing Vocational Evaluation Units, Publication (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: Training Methods in Vocational Rehabilitation, Publication (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: Vocational-Technical Report, Publication (Box 94, Folder 24)
- Box: 94, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Counseling the Disadvantaged, 1965; Publication (Box 94, Folder 25)
    Notes: March 15, 1965
- Box: 94, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Multivariate Relationships Between a Measure of Vocational Interests and a Measure of Vocational Needs, 1968; Publication (Box 94, Folder 26)
    Author: Robert M. Thorndike, David J. Weiss, Rene V. Davis
    Notes: February 1968